Saivamsi Addagada Full Stack Developer

SUMMARY

Over 2 years of experience making full stack applications and projects using popular technologies such as NextJS, NodeJS, MySQL, AWS and more. Largely self taught; learned most of what I know through online courses, tutorials, and creating personal projects. Looking to further improve my skills and gain experience within a professional setting; expanding my expertise to other fields of programming and software development.

Toronto, ON M9V3K8 +1 647-822-5813 saddagada1@gmail.com saivamsi.ca github.com/saddagada1 linkedin.com/in/saivamsi-addag

ada-32bb80293

EXPERIENCE

Uncrafted Design, Toronto, ON

Professional Development

January 2022 - Present

- Learning industry standard technologies and developing my understanding of core web application properties.
- Creating personal projects that reflect my progress and showcase my proficiency and skills.

Integrity IT Solutions, Toronto, ON

IT Field Technician

March 2019 - January 2022

- Working in partnership with Telus Communications; completing Kroll software setups, workflow and upgrades at contracted pharmacies.
- Setting up network, computers, peripherals and software in compliance with Telus and Integrity protocols.
- Completing thorough check of software to ensure peripherals are communicating correctly and pharmacists are able to fill prescriptions and carry out all necessary tasks.
- Recording and logging any issues raised during install and compiling a complete report of the install to be placed under the client's record.

Paramount Eventspace, Woodbridge, ON

Bartender

March 2019 - April 2021

- Setting up and opening bar according to the client's instructions.
- Maintaining a clean environment while serving guests in compliance with smart serve training.
- Closing, restocking and cleaning bar to ensure a safe and hygienic workspace.

SKILLS

HTML5 - 4 Years
CSS3 - 4 Years
Javascript - 3 Years
NodeJS - 3 Years
React - 3 Years
REST - 3 Years
SEO - 2 Years
Typescript - 2 Years
SQL - 2 Years
ORMs - 2 Years
GraphQL - 2 Years
tRPC - 1 Year

EDUCATION

AWS - 1 Year

Father Henry Carr C.S.S

High School Diploma September 2012 – June 2016

Toronto, ON

LANGUAGES

- English
- Telugu Fluent